[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBS", ":"], "qSentId": 9, "question": "What's the question?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "The most --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "most", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Do you really think Warren Buffet need as much attention from the government as the most vulnerable?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "think", "Warren", "Buffet", "need", "as", "much", "attention", "from", "the", "government", "as", "the", "most", "vulnerable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren Buffet"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Why are so few members of his own party properly in love with Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "so", "few", "members", "of", "his", "own", "party", "properly", "in", "love", "with", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "You know, I think there's two things at play here.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "two", "things", "at", "play", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Why doesn't he look like he wants this more?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "n't", "he", "look", "like", "he", "wants", "this", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well, I don't think anybody could come to the conclusion he doesn't want it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "anybody", "could", "come", "to", "the", "conclusion", "he", "does", "n't", "want", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "I would not be called the reserved type, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "not", "be", "called", "the", "reserved", "type", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Do you accept any of that criticism of the way he's being perceived?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "accept", "any", "of", "that", "criticism", "of", "the", "way", "he", "'s", "being", "perceived", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "No, I don't accept the criticism.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "accept", "the", "criticism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "But the fact is, what's the difference?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "fact", "is", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, well, whoa.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "well", ",", "whoa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What's the difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, the difference is that many people in the Republican Party actually think the last thing he is is severely conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "difference", "is", "that", "many", "people", "in", "the", "Republican", "Party", "actually", "think", "the", "last", "thing", "he", "is", "is", "severely", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "And that comes back to my thing at the start about the battle for the heart and soul of the party, is which way is the party instinctively now going to go?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "comes", "back", "to", "my", "thing", "at", "the", "start", "about", "the", "battle", "for", "the", "heart", "and", "soul", "of", "the", "party", ",", "is", "which", "way", "is", "the", "party", "instinctively", "now", "going", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I think you have to look at the -- at the sum of someone's record.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "have", "to", "look", "at", "the", "--", "at", "the", "sum", "of", "someone", "'s", "record", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "What are the characteristics of him that are not getting over at the moment that you see when you speak to him privately that persuaded you to put your reputation behind him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "characteristics", "of", "him", "that", "are", "not", "getting", "over", "at", "the", "moment", "that", "you", "see", "when", "you", "speak", "to", "him", "privately", "that", "persuaded", "you", "to", "put", "your", "reputation", "behind", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "One, I think he's got integrity.", "answer_tokens": ["One", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "got", "integrity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "You're not feeling the surge?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "feeling", "the", "surge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "No, I'm really not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "really", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "But if you were being critical of him in the campaign?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "were", "being", "critical", "of", "him", "in", "the", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I won't be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wo", "n't", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Not publicly.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "publicly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "So what suggestions have you already made to him that you could now repeat to me?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "suggestions", "have", "you", "already", "made", "to", "him", "that", "you", "could", "now", "repeat", "to", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "None that I'm telling you.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "that", "I", "'m", "telling", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What have we not seen so far?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "we", "not", "seen", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "It's going to come from inside him.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "come", "from", "inside", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Do you care about the poor, Governor?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "care", "about", "the", "poor", ",", "Governor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "I sure do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "sure", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "So this has to be a concern for the Republicans as they go into the proper election battle, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "this", "has", "to", "be", "a", "concern", "for", "the", "Republicans", "as", "they", "go", "into", "the", "proper", "election", "battle", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, first of all, I don't think it's my obligation to characterize the economy as a fiasco.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "my", "obligation", "to", "characterize", "the", "economy", "as", "a", "fiasco", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Did you approve, instinctively, yourself, of the bailout of the auto industry?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "approve", ",", "instinctively", ",", "yourself", ",", "of", "the", "bailout", "of", "the", "auto", "industry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Listen, you know, I've got to tell you the truth, I didn't spend a lot of time thinking about it because what I was doing at the time --", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "to", "tell", "you", "the", "truth", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "spend", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "thinking", "about", "it", "because", "what", "I", "was", "doing", "at", "the", "time", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "But now that I've asked you to think about it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "now", "that", "I", "'ve", "asked", "you", "to", "think", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, yes, but -- I mean, you know, I actually try to give things more thought than just three or four seconds before I give you an opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "but", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "actually", "try", "to", "give", "things", "more", "thought", "than", "just", "three", "or", "four", "seconds", "before", "I", "give", "you", "an", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "You've only given it three or four seconds thought?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "only", "given", "it", "three", "or", "four", "seconds", "thought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Right now, since you just asked me, and that was the context within which you put it.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "since", "you", "just", "asked", "me", ",", "and", "that", "was", "the", "context", "within", "which", "you", "put", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "But what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, listen, as I just told you, I haven't spent a lot of time thinking about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "as", "I", "just", "told", "you", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "spent", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "thinking", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "You don't have a view of the bailout of the American auto industry?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "view", "of", "the", "bailout", "of", "the", "American", "auto", "industry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "What I have is, what I have is a view of what's happening here in this state because that's my job.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "have", "is", ",", "what", "I", "have", "is", "a", "view", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "here", "in", "this", "state", "because", "that", "'s", "my", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Does he deserve it for that?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "deserve", "it", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "-- of education.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "of", "education", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Is it complex?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "complex", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Sure it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Sure it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "What is your view ideologically of bailouts?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "ideologically", "of", "bailouts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well, my view is that the government should have as little involvement in the private sector as it possibly can.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "view", "is", "that", "the", "government", "should", "have", "as", "little", "involvement", "in", "the", "private", "sector", "as", "it", "possibly", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Are you pleased it's worked?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "pleased", "it", "'s", "worked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I'm pleased people are working.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "pleased", "people", "are", "working", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Is it not a debate that's worth having, though?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "not", "a", "debate", "that", "'s", "worth", "having", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Sure it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Wouldn't that be a good thing?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "that", "be", "a", "good", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, I think what would be a good thing is for us to allow the people, the shareholders and the executives of those companies, to make their decisions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "what", "would", "be", "a", "good", "thing", "is", "for", "us", "to", "allow", "the", "people", ",", "the", "shareholders", "and", "the", "executives", "of", "those", "companies", ",", "to", "make", "their", "decisions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Because whichever you play that clip, even if you play every single word, and you take him exactly on the context you wanted it to sound like, he's still prioritizing middle class Americans in his head over the poor, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "whichever", "you", "play", "that", "clip", ",", "even", "if", "you", "play", "every", "single", "word", ",", "and", "you", "take", "him", "exactly", "on", "the", "context", "you", "wanted", "it", "to", "sound", "like", ",", "he", "'s", "still", "prioritizing", "middle", "class", "Americans", "in", "his", "head", "over", "the", "poor", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "All I could tell you is what I do.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "I", "could", "tell", "you", "is", "what", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 434, "question": "What's the question?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I -- the most vulnerable --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "the", "most", "vulnerable", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do you really think Warren Buffet needs as much attention from the government as the most vulnerable?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "think", "Warren", "Buffet", "needs", "as", "much", "attention", "from", "the", "government", "as", "the", "most", "vulnerable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren Buffet"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I got the question right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "the", "question", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren Buffet"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "You know, is it right that, taking your argument to its natural conclusion that Warren Buffet is as much in your head for his economic situation as the poorest person in New Jersey?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "is", "it", "right", "that", ",", "taking", "your", "argument", "to", "its", "natural", "conclusion", "that", "Warren", "Buffet", "is", "as", "much", "in", "your", "head", "for", "his", "economic", "situation", "as", "the", "poorest", "person", "in", "New", "Jersey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Well, first of all, Warren Buffet doesn't live in New Jersey --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "Warren", "Buffet", "does", "n't", "live", "in", "New", "Jersey", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren Buffet"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "How many billionaires are there in New Jersey?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "billionaires", "are", "there", "in", "New", "Jersey", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I don't know the answer to that question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "answer", "to", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Roughly?", "question_tokens": ["Roughly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I -- really, I have not a clue.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "really", ",", "I", "have", "not", "a", "clue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"]}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "But are all the billionaires in New Jersey, under this plan, going to get 10 percent income tax reduction?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "all", "the", "billionaires", "in", "New", "Jersey", ",", "under", "this", "plan", ",", "going", "to", "get", "10", "percent", "income", "tax", "reduction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Everybody will get 10 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "will", "get", "10", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "But are you worried you're -- you're beginning to be slightly out of touch, given that seven states now, I think, have legalized gay marriage, Washington being the latest, given that others are likely to follow?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "you", "worried", "you", "'re", "--", "you", "'re", "beginning", "to", "be", "slightly", "out", "of", "touch", ",", "given", "that", "seven", "states", "now", ",", "I", "think", ",", "have", "legalized", "gay", "marriage", ",", "Washington", "being", "the", "latest", ",", "given", "that", "others", "are", "likely", "to", "follow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Wait a second.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "second", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "So, you're suggesting that because my position is in step with 43 of the 50 states, that proves I'm out of step?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "'re", "suggesting", "that", "because", "my", "position", "is", "in", "step", "with", "43", "of", "the", "50", "states", ",", "that", "proves", "I", "'m", "out", "of", "step", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, it would have been in step with 50 of the states, but now it's only 43.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "would", "have", "been", "in", "step", "with", "50", "of", "the", "states", ",", "but", "now", "it", "'s", "only", "43", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Yes, but at what stage does it become politically strange?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "at", "what", "stage", "does", "it", "become", "politically", "strange", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I won't compromise my principles for politics.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wo", "n't", "compromise", "my", "principles", "for", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Ever?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "No, not my principles.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "my", "principles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "You would never change your mind about this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "never", "change", "your", "mind", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I would not compromise my principles for politics.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "not", "compromise", "my", "principles", "for", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Do you get flak from gay friends for this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "flak", "from", "gay", "friends", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Some, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "What do they say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "We have a robust conversation about why I have the position I have and they have the position they have.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "a", "robust", "conversation", "about", "why", "I", "have", "the", "position", "I", "have", "and", "they", "have", "the", "position", "they", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Do they -- do they accuse you directly of being bigoted?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "--", "do", "they", "accuse", "you", "directly", "of", "being", "bigoted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Would they have a right to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "they", "have", "a", "right", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "It's not a bigoted position?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "bigoted", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Again, I guess because you're a Catholic, you would be opposed to it?", "question_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "guess", "because", "you", "'re", "a", "Catholic", ",", "you", "would", "be", "opposed", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Listen, I don't have -- I don't have any problem with people using contraception.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "problem", "with", "people", "using", "contraception", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "ORGAN: It's as simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "It", "'s", "as", "simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What do you think about the whole debate that came out recently?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "whole", "debate", "that", "came", "out", "recently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I think it's a distraction and I think -- and I think that, you know, while it's a very important issue and that there are people who feel fiercely on both sides of the question of ObamaCare, not on contraception, although there is some debate about that as well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "distraction", "and", "I", "think", "--", "and", "I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "while", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "important", "issue", "and", "that", "there", "are", "people", "who", "feel", "fiercely", "on", "both", "sides", "of", "the", "question", "of", "ObamaCare", ",", "not", "on", "contraception", ",", "although", "there", "is", "some", "debate", "about", "that", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Are you personally in favor of that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "personally", "in", "favor", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, listen, you know, that's the law of the state and the legislature has put it in effect long before I came here and it's my job to enforce the law.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "law", "of", "the", "state", "and", "the", "legislature", "has", "put", "it", "in", "effect", "long", "before", "I", "came", "here", "and", "it", "'s", "my", "job", "to", "enforce", "the", "law", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "What do Americans need to be thinking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "Americans", "need", "to", "be", "thinking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "NNPS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "I think the American people should be thinking about the extraordinary gifts that this country makes available to them, of opportunity, of the ability to be able to live where you want to live, to pick the career you want to pick, and to really be restricted in this country, still today, only by what your own ambition and your willingness to work hard and to strive for.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "American", "people", "should", "be", "thinking", "about", "the", "extraordinary", "gifts", "that", "this", "country", "makes", "available", "to", "them", ",", "of", "opportunity", ",", "of", "the", "ability", "to", "be", "able", "to", "live", "where", "you", "want", "to", "live", ",", "to", "pick", "the", "career", "you", "want", "to", "pick", ",", "and", "to", "really", "be", "restricted", "in", "this", "country", ",", "still", "today", ",", "only", "by", "what", "your", "own", "ambition", "and", "your", "willingness", "to", "work", "hard", "and", "to", "strive", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "That's the American Dream at its best, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "American", "Dream", "at", "its", "best", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Only in America.", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "You would accept that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Yes, I would.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "How could that apply successfully, in your view, to America?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "that", "apply", "successfully", ",", "in", "your", "view", ",", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Make the difficult decisions without regard to anything other than what you think is in the best interests of the state.", "answer_tokens": ["Make", "the", "difficult", "decisions", "without", "regard", "to", "anything", "other", "than", "what", "you", "think", "is", "in", "the", "best", "interests", "of", "the", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "You fought 130 case?", "question_tokens": ["You", "fought", "130", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "In political corruption, we won 130 cases without a defeat.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "political", "corruption", ",", "we", "won", "130", "cases", "without", "a", "defeat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "You never lost?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "lost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Have you ever lost an election?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "lost", "an", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "How many?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "A few.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "few", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", ":", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "What did you learn about yourself from the defeats?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourself", "from", "the", "defeats", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Always to be yourself and not to get -- listen to people in your ear, the consultants and the others who try to tack you and turn you and color you, but to be yourself, because then you have no regrets.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "to", "be", "yourself", "and", "not", "to", "get", "--", "listen", "to", "people", "in", "your", "ear", ",", "the", "consultants", "and", "the", "others", "who", "try", "to", "tack", "you", "and", "turn", "you", "and", "color", "you", ",", "but", "to", "be", "yourself", ",", "because", "then", "you", "have", "no", "regrets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Can you be true to yourself completely as president or is the job simply too, now, predicated on having to deals all the time with the opposition to get anything done?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "be", "true", "to", "yourself", "completely", "as", "president", "or", "is", "the", "job", "simply", "too", ",", "now", ",", "predicated", "on", "having", "to", "deals", "all", "the", "time", "with", "the", "opposition", "to", "get", "anything", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I don't think the two are mutually exclusive.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "two", "are", "mutually", "exclusive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Can we assume that at some stage, you might run?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "assume", "that", "at", "some", "stage", ",", "you", "might", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "I don't think you can assume it, because, you know, only God knows what life brings you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "can", "assume", "it", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "only", "God", "knows", "what", "life", "brings", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "It's not your bag, is it, to do that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "your", "bag", ",", "is", "it", ",", "to", "do", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I -- no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Can I see the rest of the statehouse?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "see", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "statehouse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", ":", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "What was that -- what's the demeanor you're trying to create as you march in?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "--", "what", "'s", "the", "demeanor", "you", "'re", "trying", "to", "create", "as", "you", "march", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "I'm trying to be in charge, and to -- to give off the minute I walk through this door, to give all of the people who will be sitting here, the people of the gallery, the sense that I'm in charge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "trying", "to", "be", "in", "charge", ",", "and", "to", "--", "to", "give", "off", "the", "minute", "I", "walk", "through", "this", "door", ",", "to", "give", "all", "of", "the", "people", "who", "will", "be", "sitting", "here", ",", "the", "people", "of", "the", "gallery", ",", "the", "sense", "that", "I", "'m", "in", "charge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "It's like a mini senate, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "a", "mini", "senate", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 699, "question": "When you're standing there doing your thing -- I mean, this looks like the senate to me -- when you're standing there doing your thing, you must -- your mind must occasionally flash forward to a slightly bigger stage, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "standing", "there", "doing", "your", "thing", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "this", "looks", "like", "the", "senate", "to", "me", "--", "when", "you", "'re", "standing", "there", "doing", "your", "thing", ",", "you", "must", "--", "your", "mind", "must", "occasionally", "flash", "forward", "to", "a", "slightly", "bigger", "stage", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "What it --", "answer_tokens": ["What", "it", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "I mean, that is really what being a politician is all about, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "is", "really", "what", "being", "a", "politician", "is", "all", "about", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "Yes, it's about accomplishments, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "about", "accomplishments", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "listen, yes, you are.", "answer_tokens": ["listen", ",", "yes", ",", "you", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "You have lost quite a little weight since I last saw you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "lost", "quite", "a", "little", "weight", "since", "I", "last", "saw", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "You're now on a bit of a mission?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "now", "on", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "mission", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "You know, I'm intermittently on a mission on this stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "intermittently", "on", "a", "mission", "on", "this", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]